# SELIN CETINKAYA SOFTWARE ENGINEER

# CONTACT

AUSTIN, TX

SELIN.S.CETINKAYA@GMAIL.COM

646-912-3150

**SELINSCETINKAYA.COM** 

**LINKEDIN** 

**GITHUB** 

## **PROJECTS**

- Project1: Stock Up is a web app that allows users to categorize their shopping lists in a convenient display. I used Airtable to create an API used for creating, editing, and deleting list items dynamically, making running errands just a little bit more pleasant.
- Project2: Collaboreatery is a full-stack web-app for users to search, add, and "favorite" restaurants based on location and cuisine. The purpose of this project was to learn about building databases using Mongo as well as working in a group setting.
- Project 3: Impression is a full-stack photo-sharing web-app where users can upload, "like", and comment on photos. I employed a React front-end and a Ruby on Rails backend to build this app

# SKILLS

- Javascript
- HTML
- React
- CSS

### SUMMARY

I am a quick-thinking software engineer with a background in real estate and a passion for learning. Consistent, communicative, and thorough, I enjoy customizing solutions for a specific client or situation. With years of experience as a realtor in Austin, TX, I am skilled at quickly coming up with unique solutions to problems and look forward to future opportunities to grow as a software engineer.

## **EXPERIENCE**

#### **GENERAL ASSEMBLY**

FELLOW | FEB 20121 - MAY 2021

- Worked both collaboratively and independently to build functional applications, getting hands on experience with every step of the development process
- Planned, designed, built, and deployed full-stack web applications

#### **TEAM PRICE REAL ESTATE**

REALTOR | JUNE 2019 - MARCH 2021

- Helped buyers and renters through dozens of transactions, helping them both understand the process as well as feel comfortable and confident through what can be a stressful time in one's life
- Worked closely with clients, assessing their individual needs while creating and implementing a plan unique to each one to help them make the most of their real estate experience.

#### **HONEYCO**

SOFTWARE ENGINEER INTERN | APRIL 2016 - JULY 2017

- Provided daily support for two websites assisting the CTO with migrating on from Rails to React, while addressing bug fixes and general maintenance for another Rails site.
- Worked closely with the CEO and CTO to create timelines and planning strategies for general company growth.

# **EDUCATION**

BACHELOR OF ARTS, MAJOR IN SOCIOLOGY

HUNTER COLLEGE | 2015 - 2017

GPA: 3.94

WESLEYAN UNIVERSITY UNDERGRAD | 2013 - 2015

GENERAL ASSEMBLY SOFTWARE ENGINEERING IMMERSIVE PROGRAM | FEB-MAY 2021

#### DESIGNLAB'S DESIGN 101 COURSE | SEPT 2020

- Rails
- SQL
- Express

- Ruby
- Python
- Mongo